mytaste.in 2017-01-21

# Privacy Policy - myTaste.in

### Why do we collect information?

Your privacy is important to us. We use the information we collect to develop, analyse and improve our products. We want to give our users the best experience possible and are constantly improving the products to respond to your needs and requests. For example, we may log how often people use different features of the products, to see which ones are more popular. We also collect information to be able to offer you customized content, such as offers tailored after your gender, age or geographic location. Customized content can also appear as suggested posts or recipes, based on your previous searches.

In addition to improve our products we may send you updates such as newsletters, marketing materials and other information. (If you want to stop receiving this updates you can easily update you account settings on your profile page.) We may show you ads and offers that we think you might be interested in. We can also help you and your friends to find each other by scanning your Facebook friends or e-mail contacts. We will not sell or share your personally identifiable information with others without your express written consent. Just note that if you visit a third party websites through a hyperlink you will need to consult that site’s privacy policy for information on how they will handle information you may give to them.

### What information do we collect?

Personal Data: When you sign up on our products, you volontarily give us certain information. This can include your name, age, photo, comments, likes, email address, and any other information you provide us. If you’re using your mobile device, you can also choose to provide us with location data. You also may give us permission to access your information in other services. For example, you may link your Facebook or Twitter account to us, which allows us to obtain information from those accounts (e.g., your friends or contacts).

Log Data: When you use our products, our servers automatically record information (“log data”) including information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website or your mobile app sends when you’re using it. This log data may include your Internet Protocol address, the address of the web pages you visited that had our features, browser type and settings, the date and time of your request, and cookie data.

Cookie data: Depending on how you’re accessing our products, we may use “cookies” (a small text file sent by your computer each time you visit our website), or similar technologies to record log data. When we use cookies, we may use “session” cookies (that last until you close your browser) or “persistent” cookies (that last until you or your browser delete them).

Device Information: In addition to log data, we may also collect information about the device you’re using. That includes what type of device it is, what operating system you’re using, device settings, unique device identifiers, and crash data. To learn more about what information your device makes available to us, please also check the policies of your device manufacturer or software provide

Observe that our product is not directed to children under 13. If you learn that your minor child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us! We will nog knowingly collect personal information from children.
